Okay.
>> What's up? I'm vlogging today.
[screaming]
>> We are looking at some houses today.
We've been doing a lot of house hunting
recently, which is actually like not as
fun as I thought it would be, but it's a
process, you know. But today, we're kind
of just going to look at some fun
houses. These are very much out of our
price range right now. We're going to go
look at a million dollar house, so it's
going to be really fun. And Sunni loves
looking at houses with us. Also, if I'm
if I'm seeming a little bit glony,
I am on Lexa Pro now. How exciting. In
my last vlog, I was talking about how
I'm like super depressed and so I'm
taking Lexa Pro now. And so far, it's
been a little weird. It's giving me
weird dreams. It's giving me some
nausea. It's giving me some
derealization, like disassociation type
But that's all part of the
process. and then like hopefully it
normalizes in my body and then I just am
super happy all the time. So yeah,
that's the plan. Um, so we're going to
some open houses. We don't have our real
estate agent with us right now because,
you know, I feel like it'd be weird if I
vlogged with her. She'd probably be
like, "What are you doing?" We're also
going to go look around the area that
we're planning on moving to. And
honestly, like you guys know that I
really want to go back to California and
live there. So, like my non- adult brain
wants to do that, but my adult brain is
like that's financially irresponsible
because everything's expensive here. I'm
not even worried about like how much
water I'm using, you know? Like water is
cheap here. Water in California, not
cheap. Gas in California, it's bad. I
think like the the financially
responsible thing to do is to stay here
in North Carolina for a while. But I
actually am going to go on a trip to
California soon with my whole family.
It's going to be so fun.
Yeah, [snorts] I'm kind of Another thing
about the Lexa Pro is it's making me a
little bit like spacey. But luckily, I
have this. And yeah, that's what we're
doing today.
And I dropped Mickey off with my mom
because as much as I'd like to bring
him, he's always like, I need milk. So,
I didn't want to like deal with that
while I'm trying to look at houses. Look
at this house, you guys.
>> I'm going in.
>> Where's Micah? I'm going in my house.
>> Yeah, we're going to go in there.
Daddy's just trying to figure out how to
get in. That looks really shady, but
it's an open door.
>> But I'm like so ready to get a bigger
space. I feel like we've grown out of
the apartment.
>> Where's Daddy?
>> I think daddy failed.
>> What the hell?
>> This one is actually not available to
her.
>> Whoops.
>> Isn't this where the bump is? Yeah. Slow
down. Slow down. Slow down. And then go
fast.
>> [laughter]
>> Whoa. Way better.
>> Did you feel that?
>> Oh my god.
>> Do it again.
>> Mommy, I want to do it again.
>> Okay, we're going to go to our houses
still, but um we're going to this little
matcha place cuz we could not figure out
the the app for touring houses. But look
at this place.
>> Wo.
>> Wow. Oh, so beautiful.
>> We live here.
>> We should live here.
>> Like right here.
>> This is the monster place we're trying.
It's called Fly Kid Fly. But I've also
like I've heard mixed reviews. I've
heard that some people hate the matcha
there. So, we'll see. But it looks
really cool. Okay. Um, it was so loud
over there. But this is what I got.
This is I need to like pull up the
menu on my phone. Micah got the the
cumulus. I got some type of like
strawberry matcha. And then Sunni got a
strawberry loaf. You're not supposed to
be drinking it.
>> Here you go.
>> Thank you.
>> Ew.
>> You don't like it?
>> It looks It looks really cool.
>> Yeah. Micah's has like spirulina and
coconut. Mine has like this strawberry
foam. I'm going to try the foam.
Whoa. Holy
>> Is it good?
>> It's so sweet.
Oh, there we go. Yeah, you need you do
need to mix it. You're right. The
coconut's kind of odd.
>> Let me try yours. I kind of pressured
him into getting this one just because
it looks really cool.
>> Oh my god, this is good. I'm keeping it.
>> No, I don't like yours. I don't really
like coconut.
>> I thought you did like coconut though.
>> She wanted me to just get it cuz of the
weird name.
>> The commulus. How's your loaf?
>> This good.
>> Can you show what you got?
>> That. And what's it called?
>> Strawberry bread.
>> Strawberry to bread.
>> Two out of 10.
>> This I think I would give it like a
>> I like it.
>> You like it?
>> What do you rate your loaf?
>> Actually, I need to rate it higher
because the people in there were really
nice.
>> It's good.
>> It's so good.
>> Can I have a bite?
>> Yeah,
>> you can. M. Okay, we're going to go look
at houses now. Sunni, how exciting. Are
you so excited?
>> What do you look for in a in a potential
house that you're like thinking to buy?
>> A blue one.
>> What about like stuff inside?
>> Mhm.
>> Like do you do you like a twotory?
>> Do you like a open floor plan?
Is it working? Hey, we're in. This house
is not a million dollars, but wow, it's
really cool still.
>> Wo.
>> I think this house is still out of our
budget.
>> Oh my god.
>> First impressions. [laughter] What do
you think?
We'll just do a little tutorial cuz we
have actually done lots of house
searching, house hunting before this, so
we're kind of professionals. We found a
couple that we like.
>> Um, but we're going to continue to look.
>> I like that little nook.
>> Yep. And see, Sunni's doing a little
Sunni's doing what like the veteran
house hunters do. They check the knobs
just to see like, are people taking care
of the cabinetry? You know, she
immediately found that's a little loose.
This is something my dad does every time
I'm touring houses with him. He he goes
to the walls and he goes
>> he listens.
>> I don't know what the he's doing.
Like I don't know why he does that.
>> I feel like he's just trying to look
like he knows something that we don't.
>> Yeah, he's doing this.
>> This is kind of what you're looking for.
You're looking for things that are
different than a typical house.
>> You know, you could do
>> and good places to put your like skull
pandas and sunny angels and stuff,
>> right? You can dangle things.
>> Yeah.
>> Always fun.
>> Soon he's going upstairs.
>> Oh, see I don't like this. I don't like
when there's a railing that you can like
fall off of because I have children and
I get like uh intrusive thoughts of
that. Like I feel like
>> I don't like that.
>> But as a content creator, that's kind of
fun cuz you can do parkour. You can kind
of do like
>> remember that one family vlogger guy
that pranked his wife and made it look
like he flung his
>> Oh yeah. Yeah.
Do you love it, Sunni?
>> Oh my god, look at these sinks. They're
so little.
>> Wow,
>> dude. Look,
>> Sunni. You could wash your hands here.
And the bathtub is so small. This alone
feels like more room than what we had in
the van, even though it's not.
>> It actually might be.
>> It actually might be more of more room,
which is crazy. Check the cabinets. Make
sure there's nothing
>> What is she doing
>> wrong with everything?
>> Opening every cabinet. [laughter]
>> Do you love it here?
Yeah.
>> So, how much was this house?
>> Too bad, Sunni. It's too expensive.
[laughter]
>> Oh,
>> wait. How much was this house again?
>> It's like 650, I think.
>> 650. It's
>> cool, though, huh? Cool to see what you
can't have.
>> Let's go to a new house. You want to go
to a big house?
>> Not here.
>> You like this house?
>> Yeah.
>> The floor plan's not open enough.
Remember you were like, I want an open
floor plan.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> No, no, go.
>> This next house we're looking at is
$655,000.
You want me to show it?
>> They all look the same. Anyway,
>> damn. Well, I guess we're not buying
this house now cuz we just doxed it.
>> This is a very [clears throat]
interesting
front
entrance. Feel like all these houses are
for short people.
>> Cute.
>> Okay. Okay. Are you checking to make
sure they all work?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Let's put them back now.
[laughter]
>> Are the drawers good?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Dude, what's up with these short sinks?
We're too [snorts] tall for this. I'm
not even that tall.
>> For someone under 5 foot.
>> Look in a bathtub.
>> That is a little bathtub.
>> Dude, that's like no water can fit.
>> [laughter]
>> Why are these bathrooms for children?
This is so interesting how this keeps
happening,
>> dude. Again, with this freaking low
sink.
>> I get it. I think it's cute if you have
like one of them in like near like a
child's bedroom, but it's kind of odd.
>> Let's check out this shower, though.
>> Guys, should I take a shower in here?
>> If I was homeless, I would come to an
open house and take a shower. Wait,
let's act like she can't hear us.
Whoa. What's happening there?
>> Did you hear me scream?
Okay, let me do it.
>> She said, "Yeah,
>> Sunni, we're going to see the next
house."
You want to
>> Sunny?
>> Okay. Look at Look at the next house.
Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. You want to go see it?
>> Yeah. There's
trees around here.
>> What?
>> Okay. It's very impressive. Your
sleeping ability is very good.
Whoa. Is that like an emote?
>> Oh, sick.
>> She's hitting the wall.
>> Wow, that was so impressive.
>> Dang.
>> You hit that.
>> Yeah, you hit that.
Nice one. And we're pulling in. As soon
as you see it, give your first
impression. We can't show you the front
of the house, but we can give you a
first impression.
>> Okay, this one looks not as good as all
the other ones around it.
>> Okay, first impression. Go.
>> That was my first impression.
>> Oh, here's my impression.
>> Sorry.
>> Okay, here's mine.
>> I I want to redo cuz mine was bad.
>> No, I liked yours.
[laughter and snorts]
That's my
>> That's like initial like Oh. And then
it's like
>> And you're like, "Oh, it's actually kind
of lame."
>> Is that your initial reaction?
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah. Wait, do it. Do it. Okay. It's a
good one. You're like, "Ooh, I love that
house.
>> Oh, I love that house."
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, this one's 770K.
>> Whoa. [laughter]
>> I don't know why I thought it was 500K.
that makes sense for this neighborhood.
Um, and we won't be living here because
it's way too nice. But you can dream.
That's the That's the spirit of house
[screaming] searching. Look at this
house.
>> 67
>> Wow. Hey, let's look. Let's look around,
Sunni.
Oh,
>> guys, this is the most beautiful kitchen
I've ever seen in my life.
>> Wa.
>> And these are nice. This is a nice
upgrade
>> cuz they just vacuum out. You know how
I'm always like cooking food that's
smoking up the house? This is good to
have. Could you imagine me here? What am
I doing?
>> Burning food probably.
>> No, I'm flipping shrimp.
>> Ooh, wait. I want this house. Micah,
look at this beautiful green room.
[sighs]
Wo! Oh, look at this ergonomic tub. Big
word for me. And look, it has jets. Oh
my god, dude. Wow. [snorts]
>> You don't see this every day. If you get
tired of washing your hands here, you
just are like, "All right, I'm done with
Whoa, Sunni.
>> Sunni, don't do that."
>> No, I don't. My joke isn't funny.
[laughter]
>> Oh my god, the shower has a light
switch.
[groaning]
>> Crazy. Whoa, dude. It got this. Is it
got a
>> a shower with a light switch?
>> Oh my god. Look. It's a little vanity.
>> I've always wanted a vanity. Dude, this
is like a castle.
>> I know.
>> This This for popping your pimples.
>> Not you, but like anyone.
>> I didn't mean that as like a day.
>> You're bringing up old trauma in my
life.
>> Dude, I love the wallpaper in here.
>> Oh my god. Mimi. Mimi. It has your It
has your little
>> Well, freaking arch door.
>> An arch,
>> dude. Look at the wallpaper, though. So,
>> wait. Should we just make 700K and buy
this house?
>> Yeah.
>> How long does that take us? Like 10
years.
>> Yeah, we can do that.
>> Actually, maybe it takes us like 20
years.
>> Do you like this, S?
>> Serious?
>> Oh my god. And the light switches have
little designs on them.
>> Cute little sun room.
Cute little
house.
>> This is like an actual mansion. Why did
it look so small from the front? It's
like deceiving.
>> This is really cool.
>> Feels safer, but also looks like
>> Whoa. What in the world? This is like
the back rooms.
>> Whoa, dude.
What is in here?
Wait, [laughter] what is this? I'm so
scared. What is that? Like a tiny door.
>> This looks like a theater room, right?
Yeah. Or something like that.
Look at this
little mystery.
>> Oh, cute.
>> We could put the kids in there when
they're bad.
>> Okay,
>> dude. We would get locked in the closet.
I remember being locked in the closet
and you know like sometimes there's like
little light that comes through like the
shutters in the closet. We just be like
sticking our fingers through cuz we're
just
>> You get locked in the closet as a
punishment
>> like for timeout, you know, for like 30
minutes.
>> Why don't they just put you in your
room? Why do you have to be in a closet?
>> Cuz a room is too stimulating.
>> Oh, wa. My stripper pool could go in
here. I really want a stripper pool, you
guys. I want to get really good at it.
Oh my god. Then look at this bathroom
with the wallpaper. So cute. my
level.
>> Okay, that master bathroom though was
actually so insane.
>> What is this supposed to do? I feel like
this house seems like it's renovated,
but there's also like a lot of older
qualities about it that are nice and
like they kept some like quirky things.
>> It had like it gives it character when
it has all of that, you know?
>> It's pretty tile.
>> We're going to go outside. Can we go
outside in the backyard?
You know why the price is so low?
>> I think we dipped into South Carolina.
>> A lot of houses in South Carolina are a
lot less
cuz that is really weird that this is
700K. Guys, a house like this in
California would go for like 2 to 3
million I feel like. Right.
>> Yeah.
>> Which I feel like a lot of the houses
that we're looking at we're really
surprised by and we're like wow that's
really nice.
>> Stop. Um because we're just used to a
house that's like 500,000 and it looking
like just a twobedroom, three
bedroomedroom house,
you know, in California and it's only
like 1,500 ft² or something like that.
>> Look at these ducks.
>> Four, five, six.
>> Six of them. Are you sure?
>> Yeah.
>> Count.
>> Five 6 7 8 9 10.
>> Um maybe try counting again. And I only
I don't count that many. Yo, I actually
learned recently that birds are like
dinosaurs, apparently.
>> Right.
>> Yeah, Michael's homeschooled, so he had
like Christian textbooks
>> or dinosaurs are birds.
>> Let's go back in. I really like this
house. I want to look at the bathroom
one more time and then we can leave.
>> Guys, if you are looking for awesome
parent meth parenting methods, get one
of these. Sunni's been crying, but now
she's not because check it out. It's Mr.
Hand Sunni.
>> Sunni
color mouth.
>> Yep.
>> What's your favorite color?
>> Um, blue.
>> Like mommy.
>> Yeah.
>> Hi.
>> Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi.
>> I put the I got to hurt.
>> Are you vlogging me?
>> Yeah. Talk to.
>> Oh, I was trying to say something. um
>> has a shower,
>> huh?
>> You you
you
screamed the sh
>> spit it out.
>> You you you
scream
house shower. You screamed in it.
>> Hi.
I I'm eating the Ker. I outside. It's
going to rain. The mom is cold.
Is cold.
Stuff like that. Stuff like that.
>> A monkey.
>> Here's some info about monkey.
>> Like a monkey.
>> A monkey. Yep.
>> Yeah. I'm telling him. Guys, if you have
an Apple Watch, either don't have a baby
or have a baby and get rid of your Apple
Watch because this is no longer my Apple
Watch. This Apple Watch has become
Sunnis.
>> Sunny's Apple Watch.
>> Wow. That footage that you just saw was
from so long ago. I don't even know who
that is anymore. That's a completely
different person than who I am right
now. That footage was filmed like
literally I think three months ago when
we were looking at all those houses and
I stopped filming it because I low key
like
>> that Alexa pro was me up so I
wasn't even able to finish filming the
video. Hold on Sunni. Mommy's doing her
little intro and have fun.
>> We will have fun. We will. But I have to
say something. Some really good news
that I have for the people.
>> Which one? them.
>> Do you want to say hi to them?
>> Yes.
>> Hi,
>> guys. We found the house.
>> I feel like I kind of said that
awkwardly. Should I redo it?
>> Yeah. Do it.
>> We found the house.
>> Did it look like a real YouTuber?
>> Yeah, that looked real.
>> We found a house.
>> This is really exciting. No, it's very
very very very
exciting.
>> I think the heat is just like from the
cold.
>> It's just really hot in here. I haven't
eaten anything today. Um I've been
saving my stomach for IKEA and that's
where we are right now because I've
literally been living on Pinterest every
single day. I'm I'm scrolling on
Pinterest looking at decoration ideas
for my new house. And I really have like
the bug to buy things for my new house,
but I shouldn't. So, um we're just going
to go to IKEA and we're just going to
look around. We're not gonna buy
anything. We're just gonna look around
because I want to get inspiration for my
new house. I have like sort of a vibe
that I'm going for. I have this really
beautiful Pinterest board that I've
created. Different sections for each
part of the house. I'm like really
excited to build the most eclectic,
beautiful, unique looking space for my
children to grow up in.
>> Yeah.
>> And just to like feel super inspired
every day.
>> Yeah. Um, what is this? High five.
>> I saw like a YouTube couple. They kept
on dapping each other up.
>> So, here's the thing.
Um, I forgot.
>> Okay. So, why are you even talking?
[laughter]
>> Just interrupt me for literally no
reason. I want to go.
>> Wait, I have something important to say.
>> No, you don't. Like, no, you don't have
anything important to say. Obviously,
you don't. Yeah. So, I thought this
would be a fun little way to wrap up
this vlog. Um,
>> oh, kind of like a full circle. Like we
went and saw,
>> yeah, originally we were going to post
that content and then we were like, "No,
dude. This is depressing. We looked for
houses and didn't find anything, so we
can't post it." And so now it's like,
"Wait, we found the house and our big
idea was like, wait, let's loop it in
with the looking for a house content.
Full circle moment. We found it. Life is
epic and super great." Um, getting this
house has been kind of an up and down
journey like for both of us because
originally we were really really excited
to get the house and then when we did
all the inspections we found out that
there were like $30,000 worth of repairs
on the house, which is like um that's a
lot of money to need to have to repair a
house. Um, luckily though, our real
estate agent, she is so great. She got
all these extra people in to quote and
do things with the house and was able to
get the sellers to pay for half of the
repairs. So, we're basically entering in
with $15,000 worth of repairs on the
house, which is still quite a lot. Not
all of them are immediate. Like, one of
them would be fixing the chimney, which
is like
>> Why did you just say chim?
Chim
chim. They don't want to hear all this
okay
>> Sorry.
>> Basically, our house has like mold and
that is going to cost $15,000 to
repair.
>> Yeah. And the chimney
>> and the chimney is the roof broken. And
the roof is broken.
>> And the flooring, you guys will see
there's like some repair stuff.
>> Sadly, we don't have so much money that
we can just like buy really nice house
right off rip. But like for our first
house, we're firsttime homeowners. I'd
say like we're doing pretty good.
And I'm like 23 years old. I'm going to
be a homeowner. You're like 27, so it's
kind of like a normal age to be a
homeowner. But for me, feel like I'm
like I'm moving up in the world. Not
you, though. This is like age
appropriate for you. But for me, this is
like really epic. You know what I mean?
>> Some people don't get a house till
they're like
>> dead. They like [laughter] they never
get a house, dude. Look at that one.
>> What are you getting?
>> I want that rainbow cake. [laughter]
>> Mommy, that one.
>> Oh, the princess cake. That's very cute.
>> He's so confused. Like everywhere we
bring him. Why does he look so confused?
He's seeing this place for the first
time.
>> Oh my god, it is his first time here. I
didn't think about that.
>> Look, he wants it.
Oh my god, he really wants it.
>> Oh my god, look at Sunni.
[laughter]
>> Poor Sunni. She's so hungry.
>> This is bologoney in my stomach.
>> Oh my god,
>> these are all bologoney in my stomach.
>> Here's the spread.
It's gorgeous.
Wait, why is IKEA food actually good? Or
am I just really hungry?
>> No. Yeah, it is really good. Did you try
this?
>> Yeah, it was good.
>> I feel like when I was pregnant and we
came here, I hated the food. Like the
meatballs smelled really gross to me
when I was pregnant. That's crazy,
right? They're really good.
>> That's actually crazy, bro. That
pregnancy makes your nose like
different.
>> Yeah, that's crazy. That was longer than
that was like eight or nine months ago.
>> He's lost, man. He don't know what the
to do. I could tell.
>> Thank you, Sunni.
>> Get off.
>> Mommy, get off.
>> Okay,
>> Mickey, rate your first IKEA experience.
I think he's upset that he didn't get to
eat any of the food. Okay, not to be a
basic ass but I really really
want a doughnut lamp. Look at it.
>> Don't you just want to stick your wee
wee in it?
>> You're what?
>> Huh? But yeah.
>> Yeah, donut lamps are cool.
>> Want one of those?
>> What about What about a square?
>> No, square lamps sucks.
>> This is way cheaper than that, Mimi.
>> I wonder why. Maybe because it's not in
the shape of a donut. Micah,
>> it's a four lamp.
>> Like, get with it. I really like
this couch. I like I like fun things
like this. Yeah. For the house.
>> Yeah.
>> We'll have to find something like this.
But like that's not $1,000.
>> I like stuff that's like, you know, how
it's like, oh, the couch works well this
way, but it's like let's be goofy and
let's have it be like completely like
ovalshaped or like different. That's
what I like.
>> Yeah, it's quirky.
>> Yeah, that was something a little bit
strange.
>> That was really convoluted.
>> What a weird chair, you know. But you
like it because it's weird. Bro found
another doughnut lamp.
>> The curvature of it is really nice.
>> Okay. No, we should do a trying to
escape IKEA vlog where we like try
multiple different, you know, we'll try
a psychedelic, we'll try a stimulant,
then just wander around and then they
say go and they time you
>> and there's someone chasing us. And
[laughter] there's someone chasing you
>> and you're trying to spend the night in
IKEA without the workers finding you.
>> Oh my god. Wait, they should do like a
psyche vow and like what is your
greatest fear? Put that in IKEA with
you.
>> She has to pee.
>> No,
>> not it. Uh, you have to go bigger.
>> It's just you and me now.
>> Mickey, tell me if you see anything you
like. Okay.
This couch is so cute. Mickey.
Mickey.
Hey, Mickey.
>> Should we get that couch? Mickey. Hey,
Mickey. You think we should get that
couch?
>> The king has spoken.
>> Yeah, I didn't say anything. Yeah, he I
saw like his eyes lit up. Said yes.
>> He looks like he's just nothing's going
on. Hey.
>> Oh, he said he hated you.
>> Can you put a copy in this?
>> Uh, probably not. I mean, you could
technically. I wouldn't, though.
>> You would.
>> I love how you're thinking outside of
the box, though, Sunni. That's very
cool. I learned this with our apartment
that I need to get like glass windowed
shelves like this for like all my skull
pandas, all my little trinkets because
they get dusty so fast.
>> So when we move, I'll have to like
relocate all my trinkets. I think I need
to get something kind of like this at
some point.
>> They're going to be breathing the same
air.
>> What happens? You slowly esphyxiate.
What you exhale is like CO2, right? You
can't breathe that in. You'll go insane
and then you slowly die. Like it's a
good death, but like are you trying to
do that? What do you mean?
>> That's how do you angels? What kind of
person are you? [snorts]
>> What are you doing there?
>> For my flaky salt.
It's perfect for my flaky salt.
Should I delete this content? No
kidding. [laughter] All
right, [clears throat] come on guys.
Come on. What is he doing?
>> I want to go.
>> Come on, bro.
>> Okay. I love this when there's like
3D wall. I'm really bad with like the
terminology of everything when it comes
to like house stuff.
>> That's wine scing.
>> Wine scing.
>> Yeah,
>> that's actually what it's called.
>> Yeah.
>> How you know all this? C
>> that's trim around [clears throat]
nothing.
>> I really like this k board. It's so
cute,
>> dude. This seems like something your dad
would spank you with.
>> Bam.
Yeah.
>> No, he'd probably just like lay me on
the ground and just like hit me over and
over again
>> with with that.
>> Yeah. I'll be like
>> I'm saying like a god making it weird.
She sits in the monkey.
>> I'm [snorts] always like violating
Sunni's personal space. She's just like
used to it now.
>> Shout out horn. Come rang van
sticker hat.
>> Oh my god, look at that. This is so
cute. God,
>> Micah. So cute. Stop.
Okay.
>> What's happening?
>> A [screaming]
a little kitchen.
[snorts]
>> So cute. Micah.
>> So, we've we're in this cool spot.
Everybody's freaking out. They're like,
"Whoa, what is this? What is this? What
is this?" Um,
>> we should get Mickey another toy from
here. Mickey loves the mobile that I got
him here. That one. this one.
>> He actually really with that
thing. I think he really with the
IKEA toys. If I ever go to another rave,
I would like to have this one and like
go up to people and be like,
>> alien.
>> Hey. And they'll be like, "Get the
away from me." And I'll just keep doing
it.
>> I'm always thinking of cool stuff like
that. Oh, this is so cute.
>> Yeah, it would be funny.
Look at this.
>> That's so cute. He would love that.
>> He like lays there and he goes like
that. You should bring uh you should
bring a finger trap to a rave. Little
finger [laughter] traps and then start
putting them on people's fingers and
connecting them.
>> Hey Mickey, do you like this?
Look, he really likes it. Dang. I kind
of wish we came here for his crib cuz
they have cute colors like this. We just
have a boring white crib.
>> Your crib is kind of butt.
>> Okay, everyone's looking at me weird
that I put my baby in here. Like, is it
that weird?
>> Everyone keeps looking at me like this.
like that. I feel like he he's enjoying
himself. I'm enjoying myself.
Everything's fine. Like I don't know why
I'm getting a dirty look. You are tall
enough.
>> Yeah.
>> Sunni. I'm sorry. Guys, [snorts] we were
trying to put her in the kids section.
She really wanted to go and they said
she's like just a little bit
>> tall enough.
>> I know you are, dude. She's just a
little bit too short. And I feel so bad
for her. She really got her like I got
her hopes up. It was my fault. Let my
daughter in there. Don't you know that
my daughter is Tik Tok famous? Like so
lame.
>> Are you just letting Mickey babble into
your mic? [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> Look who's miked up now.
>> Hi.
>> Come over here.
>> Okay. I'm following you now. Sunni. Look
>> this.
>> What color is this?
>> Purple.
>> Yeah.
>> What color is this? That's yellow. Hey,
look at this. How cute.
>> No, this is brown.
>> Brown. See, this one is brown. That's
brown. That looks like the dirty bubble
from Spongebob. Dang, guys. I just
realized Sunni's never watched Spongebob
before. Am I a bad mom if I don't cuz I
don't really let her watch anything.
Like sometimes she watch she watches
Survivor or like Love Island with me.
That's probably worse than Spongebob. I
just like cover her eyes when they start
kissing. Looks like sprinkles.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. This one's your favorite color.
Blue like the sky, right?
>> No, that's my favorite color.
>> Oh, that one.
>> Yes.
>> I thought this was more of a sky blue.
You're always saying blue like the sky.
My bad.
>> That's blue.
>> That one is really pretty.
>> Hey.
>> Hi.
[laughter]
>> Hey. Stop it. Stop.
Sunni. You can't sit on that little
chair. I can't.
>> Way too little.
>> Wait, are you actually sitting on it?
>> Yes.
>> Wow. I'm very impressed.
>> See?
>> Yeah, I I see.
>> Where you should buy this?
Where you should buy this? [laughter]
>> How do you sit on this? Okay, wait.
Videape me. I bet I can sit on it.
>> Oh my god. I'm sitting on it. I'm
actually doing it. Aren't we so
talented?
>> Yes.
>> I'll buy one for you. Okay. Hey,
>> for my pet shops.
>> For your little pet shops.
>> Yes,
>> that's a good idea. Bro, they don't have
this teeny tiny little yellow shelf that
I wanted. Sunni, I'm so sad right now.
I'm so sad.
>> A
didn't give a Okay, I might get
might get one of these cactuses cuz this
cactus died. This one's really cute. I
with this one. I like that one. It
looks like a skull panda.
>> Oh, skull panda. Should I get the skull
panda one?
>> Dude, it actually looks like a little
skull panda.
So cute.
>> Looks like
they're like thick.
>> Sunni, which little tiny weird fat tree
do you want?
>> Oh, this looks It looks like an
innuendo, dude. Wait, this is actually
the most epic tree ever.
[laughter]
>> What are you doing?
>> I was like 5 years old.
>> That is crazy.
He's so happy.
>> What?
>> I just This whole IKEA trip you've been
like so downcast, you know? You're like
smiling ear to ear.
>> This is the funniest thing ever. I can't
wait to show your brothers. They're
going to love this.
>> My brothers, they do love a good
innuendo. They're at that age. Are you
okay? Okay. Careful. Wow, dude. She
keeps falling down here. She's like an
Animal Crossing character when it has
like bad luck.
>> Does that happen to her?
>> Yeah, she falls like an Animal Crossing
character, too.
>> Should we switch out that cactus?
>> No.
>> Do the other one? Well, because did you
know it's actually bad for the plant?
Like, they don't live long. They They
have to graft the top of it onto the
bottom.
>> What?
>> They take two c different types of cacti
and they graft it together. And it's
honestly, it's unethical.
>> I think the quality of life is bad. and
they end up not living very long.
>> Oh my god, my good.
>> But we can still get it. It's fine. I
don't mind purchasing something that's
unethical.
>> Panda. Okay, I I'll leave it here if you
let me buy the new Skull Panda series.
>> No, let's get the cactus.
>> Oh, you want me to leave it here?
>> No, let's get him. It's fine. It's fine.
He'll just
>> I'm still going to buy the new Skull
Panda series.
>> They made um Skull Panda hippers.
>> I don't keep up with that stuff.
>> Super lit.
>> I feel like now that I'm a parent, it's
like I kind of stopped playing
Bionicles. I got rid of my Legos. I kind
of like I'm like a, you know, I'm an
adult.
>> Well, that's actually because you're 27
years old, Micah. I'm still 23.
>> I still need to buy my little
>> a couple of years in you.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Fair enough.
>> Collecting.
>> That's fair enough.
>> You're right. My fault, [crying]
>> bro. What are you talking about?
>> Hey, he waved. Mimi, he waved.
>> Wait. Wait. No, he's actually smart.
Not because Ow. Oh my god.
>> Do you poke the cactus?
>> Put my entire hand on top of the cactus.
>> Yeah, dude. I'm getting tired in
here. I don't know what it is about
IKEA, but it makes me kind of
>> It's an You know what the issue is?
Meatballs after after you go through
everything. Meatballs before then you
start digesting and you're not supposed
to move. You're not honestly you're not
supposed to eat a big meal and like
work.
You're kind of supposed to um you're
kind of supposed to eat and then like do
a little bit of light movement, but too
much heavy movement
is kind of stops the blood flow to the
stomach and your body's like working to
try to digest whatever.
>> Wait, wait, stop talking.
>> I know you have some text.
>> Oh, hi.
>> Hi, [laughter]
>> you guys.
My super sexy, amazing, hot boyfriend is
getting me to donut land.
>> So, everyone be jealous of me.
>> Uh, it's too far away.
>> Oh,
>> See, we're right here.
>> Yeah.
>> We got to go all the way back to the
lighting, your home, and electronics.
>> Mickey, can you go run and get
>> I really want you to be happy, but my
dick?
>> Not that much, you know.
>> What is she doing, bro?
Oh my god. What's going on? Sunni, what
are you doing?
>> Oh my god. She's just going too fast for
my liking.
>> Oh Here's some lights.
>> No, I don't like that one. I don't want
a ball light. I want a donut light.
>> Let's just get a ball light.
>> I don't want to fall away.
You guys are literally the same person
just different
>> different.
>> Thank you.
>> Oh my god,
>> Sunni.
>> Donut lamp.
>> Donuts.
>> Thank you, Micah. You guys look at my
donut [laughter] eyes.
[clears throat] Looks so good.
Yeah, the room's looking really good.
I actually I just realized that all the
lights in here are from IKEA. Now I'm
kind of embarrassed. I just I really
like Good light. And look what I can do.
>> This light's not from IKEA.
>> Oh yeah, we don't even use that one. I
used it so much when I was nursing
Mickey. [laughter]
>> I would turn it on and I just be like,
"Wake up." I like
feed him.
>> Yeah.
>> Wow.
>> You know how people always do flips onto
a surface below them? Have you ever
thought about doing a flip onto a
surface higher than you?
>> Oo. Are you going to do it?
>> Yeah.
>> You're going to do it?
That's really exciting.
Wow.
I didn't know you could do that.
Do it again. Do a back flip now. No, I
mean do a back flip onto the bed.
Okay. [laughter] Okay.
Okay, maybe try like a barrel roll.
[laughter]
Can you do the front flip again?
Dang. You know what? We should end every
single vlog with a cool trick.
>> Cool party trick or something.
>> Yeah. Okay.
Subscribe for more cool tricks.